On today's episode of the Command Center
podcast, boys.
>> Yes,
>> we won free agency.
>> Did we?
>> We talk about why that's important, if
it is important, and then what's the
most important thing for long-term
success. Is it the quarterback? Is it
the head coach? Is it both? And then
we've got a five round commanders mock
draft. It all starts right now.
>> Welcome to the Command Center podcast.
I'm Logan Pollson here with Fred Smoot
and Santana Moss. And as always, we're
presented by Big Bear AI, mission ready
AI for a rapidly evolving world. And we
are in the Big Bear AI command center
studio.
>> Mhm.
>> Boys, how we doing?
>> Uh, great.
>> Yeah. How's the weekend, by the way,
>> man? Look, 85°, cannot beat it. But then
it comes back and now it's 40°. How you
feeling?
>> The weather's been a little
schizophrenic here, coach.
>> Look, it got me like this.
>> Yeah, I'm done with it. I'm I'm tired of
it.
>> What was that, two weeks ago? It was
like a tornado.
>> No, a hurricane.
Like that's what it is. The if a
groundhouse see one more time, I'm about
to lose it.
>> Yeah. And I will say March in Virginia
tends to be a little bit
>> hectic. This feels a little bit more
It's snowed.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. It snowed and it was 85 in the
same month. That's what you get. I think
we forget sometime we are in the
mountains.
>> Yeah.
>> And I think we forget that. We are We
are right in the Appalachian Mountains
and I think we forget that sometimes.
>> Yeah. No doubt. Um, so let's do some
housekeeping real quick. So we've got
football
>> football
>> Columbia vers France Sunday, March 29th
at 300 p.m.
>> Mhm.
>> And I didn't tell you this, boys, but
I'm thinking about getting in like a Rex
soccer league, but I don't know if
that's the right move for your boy at
this stage.
>> I don't know what the with with your
feet. I don't know if they quick enough
to play soccer.
>> So it's not it's like it's just about
the touch. The touch on the football. I
got to see angles. The thing I'm worried
about is like, you know, you get
competitive. Yeah. And you start to like
run
>> and then you get that like little oh
hammy little groin.
>> Yeah. I to say man like soccer is
non-stop running. I hope you understand
it.
>> So dude I you know I grew up playing
soccer right. So I played
>> you told me about that. Yeah.
>> So I played for a long time. I had a
scholarship offer to play soccer. So I
was like oh maybe my sister-in-law is
playing in the league. She's like come
play be an alter.
>> Was you a goalie?
>> No I actually played uh like I don't
know if you know the positions I played
stopper like defensive midfield. So like
on like goal kicks, punts from the
keeper like you go up and you
>> win those. you kind of control the
defensive middle of the field. So, um
yeah, I mean it helped that I was 6'4
and
>> 215.
>> So, is soccer like one of those sports
that you never forget? Cuz like it it
seems to me it's it's a little harder
than what we do.
>> It's like uh in terms of like skill
you're saying?
>> I think it's like anything like there's
always like a little bit of skill
associated with it. Reminds me like
basketball, you know, like you know, you
got the crossovers on the dribbles and
stuff and sometimes you if you don't
practice,
>> you lose a little bit of that feel.
Yeah. Um, but yeah, so just remember
Colia vers France, Sunday, March 29th, 3
p.m. But in the meantime, um, producer
Jason has set some up for us here real
quick. We've got, uh, Laramie Tonsil's
presser, which I have not heard. Have
you guys heard it?
>> Yeah, I haven't heard it.
>> Not at all.
>> And he was he was giddy about this when
we came in. This is good stuff.
>> Well, I I did see him uh I see all the
players waited on him when he when he
was signing his contract. So, that show
you a lot, man. You know, people don't
do that for offensive line. They do it
they do it for wide receivers. They do
it for quarterbacks, running backs, but
to see offensive lineman have that much
praise from his team. That says
everything, man.
>> Also, I didn't realize this. I was
talking to a guy that I train. Um he's
familiar to the DV Morgan Moses and he
was like, you know, he's the first $30
million tackle. So, kind of hitting a
milestone. Yeah. Cuz I thought, oh,
Trent, he was like, "Oh, Trent was I
think it was 275 for a while." Yeah. So,
you know, he's he hit a milestone. It's
pretty cool for Larry. But you know, the
next man up, I always get three more
dollars than the last man. And that's
what it is. Like, think about it. We got
a
>> uh I guess Jackson Smith and Jigma is a
$42 million a year receiver.
>> And so, just to tease this, we're going
to do a draft segment later where we're
going to go through like a five round
mock. Yeah.
>> And we're going to talk about this
because I do think the free agent market
for receiver, the free agent market for
running back
>> has to factor in to Guys, think about
this. Okay, I'm going to jump the gun
here a little bit. What did the guy from
Seattle make when he went to um Kansas
City? Do you know
>> Seattle? Who?
>> Yeah, the running back can $14 million.
He's the number one running back. He
made $14 million. Jackson Smith and
Jigba
>> 42 million.
>> 42.
>> That is ridiculous.
>> 40 years
>> $30 million difference. So that has to
factor in a player and being a a a
former receiver in this league. It's no
it's no way.
>> And I'm I'm being real. I've been saying
this though for the last few years. Like
it's no way that we think that less of
our running backs now. You know what I'm
saying?
>> Especially cuz that running back's going
to touch the ball 20 times and the
receiver in a good game.
>> The majority of the time we we stuffing
that damn ball in that running back's
belly. So
>> it's the discrepancies are crazy cuz and
I'm not I'm not
>> I hate corner and safety the same way,
right?
>> Yeah. I mean corners the price tag's
going up. Safety is kind of leveled off.
>> Flat lining.
>> But I I just I don't It's a lot of
money, man. Listen, it's a lot of money.
I seen that 160 come across this screen
>> cuz think about how the running back and
I understand cuz they committee things
nowadays running back by committee it's
more guys touching the ball you don't
have guys back there every down they
still get more to load than we do you
know
>> absolutely all right so we got a little
sidetracked there but we got uh Laramie
Tonsel press
>> yeah so this press conference uh Nikki
Javala made this cut and put it together
on X so you can follow her to see this
specific cut uh it's kind of like the
best moments from it so I just want to
get you guys reaction to him cuz uh I
think it's a fantastic presser. So,
>> okay.
>> Oh, there he is.
>> I'm acting my age like I don't know how
to use Zoom. Hold on. Give me one. This
is crazy.
Um I don't know. Maybe because I'm a
great player.
>> Why has extension got done quickly?
>> Absolutely. Um, you know, I wanted to I
wanted to get the the deal done quicker
than normal and for sure uh get more
money in that bank account. So, I wanted
to get it done fast.
So, I tell the guys, you know, if you
want to come get bigger, stronger,
faster, come work with me. Just look,
just look how big my back is, you know?
Come get a big back with me. You know,
>> funny story I try to tell my son like,
you know, dad just, you know, got more
money like I, you know, I reseted the
market again and my my son was like,
does that mean I'm rich?
>> There he is,
>> dude.
>> Mad respect though.
>> Hey, I tell you this. We all been there
when they when when they saying you fa
to sign on that line or when you sign on
that line and that that check a little
fatter than what it used to be.
>> Yeah.
>> That that he's showing you that look
man, I'm I'm highly favored right now.
I'm blessed and and I'm going to enjoy
it. I'm not going to sit here and be
like sugar coat it.
>> It's a blessing. Yeah. It's a blessing.
But I'm going to let you know how much
of a blessing. So hats off to him.
>> He earned it. He earned that money. He
earned it. Reshape the market. And he
not afraid to talk about it, man. I'm
playing the game cuz I love the game,
but I also love the money that the game
gives to me. So, it's nothing wrong with
it. Everybody in their job want to be
want to raise
>> and they're not as afraid to. So, a
lawyer can talk about how much money
they make, but if an athlete talk about
how much money they make, get something
wrong with
>> Well, the other thing when you're an
athlete, people can just look it up.
>> It's everywhere. It's on like every
service imaginable. And the other thing,
too, that I I this is something that I
experienced when I played, again, I came
from a suburban community in LA. Not
super rich, but not poor. Kind of right
in the middle. And when you come to an
NFL team, you get guys that are that
were rich, you know, former athletes,
kids that are around, also get guys that
are really poor. And you kind of realize
like that money
>> means something different
>> to those guys that changes lives
>> and it it changes their lives. He talked
about his son in that family.
>> It like that's going to change his
grandkids, his like he is now
generationally wealthy, which is
something that he's earned. He's put his
body through that. And that's something
that I always that coming and playing in
the NFL
>> reminded you of because in college when
we played there was no money floating
around that same way for you maybe but
>> be talking about it. Don't look at me
like that. DON'T BE TRYING TO THROW
MISSISSIPPI STATE UNDER THE BUS.
>> Mississippi State define institution in
the SEC. But
>> don't throw us under.
>> No, but I feel him though, man. I'm, you
know, it it just me listening to it, it
remind me of how I felt. You know, I I
didn't have a presser like that to talk
about, you know, the feeling. I probably
did, but it was probably quick cuz I,
you know, back in them days, I wasn't
trying to be in front of the mic too
long. Um, but man, it's such a great
feeling, bro. And not only just because
you're getting paid, it's because the
hard work that you've you put it off
>> from day one has continuously blessed
you. You know what I mean? Every time
>> work too.
>> Yeah, that too. And then you can see it.
I mean, I'm not sure how you guys, you
know, you guys family operate, but I
remember signing new deals or getting
new money and before I was able to even,
you know, be excited, family hitting you
up. Hey,
>> they like they got
>> WE DIDN'T
WE RICH, [__]
>> NAH, but it's just one of those things,
man. Like I'm I'm sitting here smiling
about it inside and probably I'm I'm not
sure if I smirked enough on camera just
listening to him, but even now I don't
know how how motivated you guys are, but
that's how that's I think like that
every day. Like whatever you putting out
there comes back. So I never I've never
not had that feeling of it's a time to
make more. It's a time to do more. It's
a time to be more successful. That's how
I live my life. like I'm always thinking
about a way of making something more out
of what I have. And so to see that
>> um a game that we learned as kids is
able to continuously, like I say, bless
you.
>> As a player of his magnitude,
>> you know, you don't know. You say,
"Okay, I get two contracts."
>> Well, this is what, three for him. This
third one.
>> He's reset the tackle marketice. Twice.
>> That's what I'm saying. So, just think
about it. Like, when we was playing, we
was
>> praying to get two. Yeah,
>> probably want to get my second deal cuz
you get that second deal now you know
you can second deal says I'm I'm
extending the you can you can ride
sunset with that second deal. I remember
getting into the league and the veterans
like boy you get that second deal that's
going to put you put you up there. You
know what I'm saying? You just this guy
this his fourth one and he's a tackle so
you know that money is ridiculous.
>> It ain't going to stop.
>> So yeah, you know what's crazy is I'm
with you. Let me hold a dollar.
>> He structured the steer so he could
maybe do it one more time.
>> No no tackles. Trent is 3 what? Seven.
>> He's my We're the same age. So 30. I
just turned 39. So he's 38.
>> 38.
>> Tackles like big boys can play this game
longer than small.
>> Obviously I do like the personal
training like strength conditioning
stuff on the side. And one of the things
that is like when you do the research on
it like heavyweight boxers age better
than
>> than like with the weights
>> because quickness deteriorates more
quickly than powerrengint, right? And so
these guys are big explosive powerful
athletes. They can keep that running for
a little bit longer, which is pretty
cool.
>> Yep. You could tell when that sports car
start to slow down.
>> But that SUV
>> or that that big semi.
>> Yeah. They just going to keep trucking.
That's the thing about And I was told
that cuz I remember talking to Bruce
Smith when I first got here. He like,
"Man, y'all coners, y'all wide
receivers. Once you lose y'all speed,
y'all out of here." He like, "But us
Dline.
>> Yeah,
>> we in it.
>> You don't know when we slow down." BUT I
WAS LIKE, "YOU RIGHT." But I will say
this though, and this is something that
I talk about so much with my friends and
we talk about just guys who come in as a
skilled guy, slow,
>> yeah,
>> it's over for them. If I come in as a
fast, super fast guy,
>> it's never over for me cuz now I can be
a possession guy and my possession gears
is is way faster than that other guy who
came in at 45. My four five has a
different kind of, you know, uh, you
know, hump to it. Bingo. So, so I I
wouldn't just say it's quite over for a
guy who's highly like one of those
sports cars, those those Lamborghinis,
those Ferrari.
>> One thing we can say about them
Lamborghinis, Ferrari, they high
maintenance and we are a skinny dude.
>> I will say this, like you come in like
one of the reasons like we do the
combine and you see that 43 on there is
to me it implies speed reserve.
>> So Tann you were just talking about this
in in the when we're getting ready for
the show like as you get older the game
slows down. you also slow down. But if
you go from a 43
to a 445, like that's still fast, right?
So for me, like my slow ass, right? I
ran a 49. Like when I got slow, that
thing's a 52.
>> There's guards running fast, right? You
know what I mean? It got a little got a
little dicey quicker than I wanted it
to. So, um, you know, that's that's one
of the things that we're we're talking
about there. But anyway, um, really
happy for Laramie, happy for his family,
glad he is here.
>> Let me hold your dollar, man. Oh, and
then uh Jason, what we got before we hit
the break? Oh, we got break one here.
You ready to go?
>> Okay,
>> so what do we got?
>> Break one. Okay, guys, we have the chain
and the trophy.
>> Present. So, here are the results.
>> Man, I already know how they just be
playing favorites.
>> Where do you get these, Jason? Where do
they get the votes? Off the YouTube
page.
>> This is off YouTube. I actually have
comments.
>> Oh,
>> so get ready.
>> All right, what do we got?
>> All right, give that trophy to Dr.
Pollson.
Got a vote there.
>> I got a couple pity votes.
>> We have another one here that says, "My
vote is for Logan
>> just because I know he won't get many
and we love you."
>> So, there's that one.
>> Uh, okay. And then we have uh a little
bit of a runaway here.
>> Uh, we had uh Smoot, you put the chain
on and immediately became Ron Burgundy.
>> Uh, here's another vote for Logan.
>> I'm killing it, boys. But guys, the top
comment of the week was
for Senora Santana.
>> Senora Santana. Yeah. And it and it has
21 likes.
>> Well, also that was what he said. Senor
Sant talking about his Spanish class,
right?
>> Yeah. To give you a hard time.
>> Underneath this is for voting.
>> Okay.
>> So, people are responding to the voting.
It goes to Santana. And just to
emphasize, someone broke this down.
>> Yeah.
>> Round one, it did go to you, Smoot. Oh,
>> round two went to Tana and round three.
>> Round three went to you, Smoot. So, you
would be like, wait, I won. It was like,
nah, that's that West Virginia.
>> I'm so tired of that read.
>> Do you want to So good.
>> You want it this week?
>> No. Hey, you're you're winning a lot.
You're complaining a lot about it.
>> All I'm saying is it's that same damn
read.
>> No, but see, this is the thing. You
heard what he just said. I'm so tired of
that read.
>> Hey, it is a nice read, man.
>> It's It's a wellwritten read.
>> Yeah, he gonna have to put the goat on.
>> I'll put it on, man. Let me put it on.
>> Yeah, dude. Look at that thing.
>> It's heavier than you think.
>> Where my chain,
>> dude. Wow. Look at that.
>> Every time I come around, you see that
bling bling.
>> I thought I was going to get today about
fit that bling bling.
>> Man, I'm so tired of these mama.
>> Bling bling blinging bling. So, what I'm
saying, do you want to switch the reads
up? Would that be helpful for you? Cuz I
mean, tennis like it's tannis, but if
you want to give it a shot.
>> Listen, I'm getting my love from a big
bear AI. All right. That where my love
coming from. That's how I won the round
one.
I listen fans.
>> All right, let's pay some bills.
When the mission is critical and
readiness matters, Big Bear.ai AI
delivers proven AI technology and
expertise to help safeguard national
security and critical infrastructure.
This mission ready AI big barrel.ai
official partner of the Washington
Commanders.
>> It's very good. Very good. Very good.
Very good.
>> Commander fans, your fandom just got an
upgrade. Introducing the AAA Commander
MVP membership where real fans gets real
perks and same trusted AAA membership
benefits. The new AAA Commander
membership provides a chance to win game
tickets, access to VIP events and
experiences. 15% off Commander online
pro shop while providing peace of mind
for Commander fans on the road. Already
aaa member? Don't sit on the sideline.
Upgrade your membership or join today
ata.com/commanders.
>> Damn. Carol City High School.
>> Let's go, dude. It's He's got the He's
got a little more character to him.
>> Might be the might be the bling bling
bling bling.
>> I'VE BEEN TRYING TO GIVE HIM THE
ALREADY.
>> I'm just saying I'm just That's my
observation. You guys decide at home
what you think.
>> You know what? This is such an offensive
defensive thing in here. I can see the
divide in here. I'm just let me um let
me take a picture of my my goat chain.
>> Dude, look at him.
>> Hey, I love it, man. That was He came
out strong. You got You definitely have
it. And Okay. So, uphill climbs.
>> Never scared of competition. Okay. Have
you played Cona?
>> All I know is he's got the West Virginia
read coming up on deck here soon. And
you got to you got to nail that next
read, bro.
>> Listen, Geico going to get everything I
got.
>> All right. So, obviously coming out of
free agency and the question is or no,
the not a question because there's no
questions here is we won free agency
powered by Big Bear AI mission ready AI
for a rapidly evolving world. So,
obviously we had a bunch of free agent
signings. We have reserved future
contracts pending for guys that you know
practice squadman roster guys and we've
got two new coaches coming in right
David Blau uh Donte Jones right so
offensive defensive coordinator there
respectively it feels like there's a lot
of change here a lot of excitement and
the question then becomes did we the
Washington commanders win free agency
and can you win free agency at this time
of year which is what March yeah
>> 23rd
>> I don't want to put the word win free
agency I Never. I didn't like it when I
played. I don't like it now. What we did
do is get better. Like that's all I care
about. Did we get better with our
weaknesses? Our weakness edge rushing.
We got better. Uh we upgraded at
linebacker. All right. We we we upgraded
at tight end. All right. Did we upgrade
positional uh value and positional
rooms? Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. All
right. Got better even with the coaches.
All right. They we we upgrading at every
spot. So I don't like to say win free
agency cuz sometime that means we just
signed the best free agent available.
And the one thing about free agency is
it's bidding wars. So yes, you overpay
for talent because you bid on talent.
All right. But win, no, you don't win in
the offseason. You win in the end
season.
>> Yeah. I think the only thing about
putting a win on free agency, you don't
really play a game.
>> Yeah.
>> You play to win the game. You see what
I'm saying? And when you don't have a
chance to really play with those guys
that you just selected, who knows who
won? Because you can go out there and
pick a bunch of names that no one heard
of.
>> But guess what? Come training camp, come
regular season, these guys mesh better
than anybody you ever heard of on any
other team because they just had the
right foundation already. They just
needed to add pieces
>> and the right flow.
>> I look at this, man. Look, I'm I'm
Give me a word for it. Um, I'm blown I
was blown out of my seat by how we went
out there and attacked every position
that was there.
>> And still got 50 million left.
>> Bingo. Had had money on on reserve for
whatever else going to be sitting around
there. You see what I'm saying? So I I'm
I'm
>> I'm more than ecstatic to know what this
could become.
>> But you have to play the game.
>> You still got to go out there and be
healthy, which is the the the top, you
know, what you call them in in all this.
You have to have a healthy team. You
have to have the guy who's going to lead
that ship be out there and be and and be
one of those guys leading that ship. And
then all these guys have to be able to
mesh and play together. And so when they
say we won it, I remember what couple of
hours into free agency, THE FANS WAS
UPSET.
>> MHM.
>> But by the time we got out of it,
everybody happy now. You know what I
mean? So it's always going to be up and
down. It's a it's a seesaw of views. You
feel what I'm saying? Right now, I think
we're up because everybody's just so
excited about these names and all the
all the positions, all the key guys, but
until we play the game, I can't put a
win on it.
>> And so, to Fred's point, right, it's not
I think the thing that gets me excited
is that these are good fits. At least on
paper, they're great fits if you ask me.
>> So, you know, obviously Adafo, defensive
end, an ascending player that we fits a
an area of need, but I think
>> hasn't peaked yet. I loved it.
>> Hasn't peaked yet. I think that's
exactly right. Look at Chika Conquo kind
of this move tight end piece. got a
receiver skill set. How does that fit in
the David Blau offense? I think about
Sam Leapora, obviously Hawinson in
Minnesota, the two places that he's
drawing from know to use that weapon at
a high level. Leo Chanel, this kind of
offball player attacks down
coverage like and the thing is that Fred
said there is they're all ascending. So
when it comes to winning free agency,
because again I agree with Tanny, you
can't like win it. There's no game.
>> There's no score to be kept.
>> I think and this is just one man's
opinion that this is the right way to do
it. Yeah,
>> you get guys with good contract value
that fits that projected roles and if
they hit on those roles and those
opportunities like it'll it'll lead to
wins in the season, I think is what I'm
trying.
>> How about this? How about this going
forward?
>> If we can stack wins in every phase of
us getting to the to the regular season,
then we have a great chance to go out
there and win the regular season. You
see what I'm saying?
>> So, we won.
>> You won a march.
>> Let's go win the draft.
>> Let's go win the draft. Yeah. then let's
go win training camp. You see what I'm
saying? Then now now let's go out there
and dominate this regular season and go
out there and win the postseason and and
have a Super Bowl, you know, trophy to
host up.
>> What I do like about some of these guys
we say most of them come from winning
coaches. Like when you come from a
winning culture, you bleed winning. You
only know winning and you could teach
everybody else how to win consistently.
>> And it almost too g me that vibe of year
one when a lot of these guys didn't
wasn't long long tenders. They we like
hey we going to give him a year. we get
this guy a year.
>> And those guys went out there and
executed because they knew I got one
year. I got one year to get this thing
done. Whether I'm going to be back here
or somewhere else, I got to go out there
and play my best. So, I almost feel like
we took a page out of that book. Say,
"Hey, man, we just got to get these guys
in the building cuz for what they did
last year, they deserve to be over here.
We deserve to take a chance on its
>> and hopefully if they can go out there
and dominate and play the way we want
them to play, then we can be talking
about, you know, something longer come
next year." I just like we didn't go out
there and sign one gigantic contract and
thought we won.
>> We went out there and we spaced it out.
We we we we we brought a group in. It
changes the average age. It it the
speed, the length, the strength. Yeah. I
I I enjoy that.
>> And I think that's the thing. It's a
four year for Adafoa. It's a a threeyear
for Chika, three year for um three year
for Tim Settle. Welcome home. And then I
like the idea of like um uh Caleb von
Chason, right? Yeah. Like at one year
kind of a one year 12 million bucks,
prove it type of deal. Like he played
really well.
>> No, especially in the playoffs
>> in New England last year. He played
really well last year. And so a lot of
people were like, "Hey, show us again."
He seems like the perfect candidate for
show me again. Let's see what you got
and and kind of grow into that role um
you know, for the Washington. But I also
think resigning Trayon Burks, I just I
feel like he's going to have one of
those seasons. I feel like it's been
brewing for him. For the first time, he
healthy.
>> I think that's healthy, right?
>> Yeah. For the first time, he's healthy,
but he also got a franchise that's
loving on him. And that's different.
>> And and the expectations might be a
little lower than it was coming in and
being the first place. Yeah. You know, I
mean, you got to think a lot of that
stuff is what kind of weighs on players.
You know, it's not it's just not so much
of just saying, "Hey, go out here and
show me." It's like, "No, we need to see
that right now." Because I remember
being a jet.
>> And when you get hurt and I got hurt out
the gate and now I'm just walking around
and they like,
>> "Who are you?"
>> Like, "What's up?" Like, "You going to
show something?" I'm like, "Mom, I got a
whole brace on my leg right now. What
can I show you?" But that's how it is
because
>> we spent this money. We want to see
something now. We can't We don't We
can't afford for you to be sitting back.
You talking about you the one that's
injured. We we could take anybody else
that we drafted and they be the ones on
the shelf but not you. So I think when
you get all that off you off your plate
off your shoulders. You not carry that
around. You have a guy like Terry that
you can say I'm I'm looking up to him
because he's going to carry the load.
All I got to do is just do do my part
>> and look I can go out here and play
mistake free or confident and with a
clear mind and clear head and go out
there.
>> And also being at number two opens it up
cuz you Terry going to get the doubles.
>> Now you can go ahead and go to work. And
that's the thing I maybe we can have
this conversation now or maybe after the
draft. We'll see when when's the pro,
but like we can kind of allude to it
here. That's something that still needs
to be probably addressed a little bit,
right? Is that number two receiver spot
you got guys like Burks, Luke McAffrey,
Jaylen Lane, Van Jefferson coming in
where and Deami kind of as a pitch
hitter, but like it still feels like you
need
>> but I don't I don't think you
necessarily need a when when you have a
when you have a core of guys
>> Yeah. one can stand out in front of
everybody and everybody else just do
their part because I don't I don't think
you need a a solidified number two when
you have a a number one
>> when you think a guy do you think that
so you think kind of like number two by
committee
>> two by committee I was we not successful
year one of Jaden's um rookie year with
those man look Dami played so well
>> in in the postseason he was number two
receiver you see what I'm saying but you
couldn't tell me that uh your guy who
went to Chicago the kids wasn't, you
know, he he wasn't helpful in our whole
getting to the postseason. You couldn't
tell me that the other guys, you know,
who stepped up and made plays wasn't. So
that's why I'm saying like when you have
a committee of like, man, we got all
these guys that can really go out there
and be dominant. Like they can be twos
or threes somewhere else. Now they on
one. They vot.
>> They come in together. We You be y'all
be voted.
>> Y'all be Voltron. We got Optimus Prime
or whatever you want to call Terry.
Scary Terry. You can name him whatever.
superhero you want, but we got him over
there. We know when in doubt, he's going
to he's going to perform.
>> So, do you So, this is Do you think that
they are good at receiver? Like, or do
you think that could I move into the
season with this group? I can move into
the season, but I won't I would So, I've
been hearing folks talking about, hey,
we can still get this person free agency
wise. I don't really necessarily need
that.
>> I'm thinking about the draft more. I'm
saying I'm saying get me a draft piece
>> that can come in and say he has
potential to be our our guy in the
future. Yeah.
>> To go along with this this crew.
>> Is that does that need to be at seven or
can that be at seven?
>> No, they got they got to be later like
Elijah Sak from from Indiana or somebody
in the in the third round, fourth round.
I don't need it to be the first round. I
>> But I look at contract. I'm not I'm not
in I know how you are about I'm like I'm
like if a guy there at seven and he's a
receiver that you feel like that could
come in and be your number one
>> trust your grade right like yeah
>> go get them.
>> Yeah I'm with you. So again like that's
a position I'm glad we had that
conversation cuz it feels like it feels
like they could use more but the Voltron
analogy. I like that quite a bit. And
then in the draft getting a young piece
>> to build.
>> You get you get a young piece in here
with with the veteran leadership that
you got. I'm talking about a young
piece. Not a young piece that we saying
that has potential to start one day. a
young piece. You said, "Man, this guy
can come out here right now and dominate
and start right now."
>> Watch how that room sets on fighting
because now all them guys like you might
not be.
>> No, no, I need to step it up.
>> Step it up. See what I'm saying? You get
a guy here that can move the dog on
needle,
>> man. Make him different than everybody.
Bring in a Malachi Fields that's 6'4,
230, don't look like nobody else in the
room and you can get him second day,
third day. Like, so it's options out
here. And I I hate when people think for
me to get a ball and he got to be in the
first 100 picks. That ain't that ain't
football, man.
>> Especially this year. I mean, like right
now, like you're looking at like Mel
Kyper, Todd McShet, Daniel Jeremiah.
They've got 20 receivers graded with top
100 grades, which would be a record if
all those guys went there, right? So
like I look at again Malachi Fields,
Elijah Sherrod, you know, Josh Cameron
from Baylor. Like there's guys there at
71. You say, "Man, that guy could be
special." like Deshan Stribbling from
Old Miss. Like I do love him, man. You
know, he's 6'2, he ran a 43. Like he's a
competitive son of a gun. So like, but
again, like I like all the guys we just
talked about. And so who do I like the
most at 71, but I don't think it
precludes you from looking at seven
either, right? It just depends on what
your board looks like.
>> That's why you do what you did in free
agent. So I could take best player
available with every pick.
>> Yeah. So the other position I want to
talk about real quick is running back,
right? because that's getting a lot of
buzz because of Jeremiah Love, all those
different things.
>> That feels like again it's a good room,
not a great room. They've got good death
pieces like Rashard White for what he
is, right? Kind of one of the better
receiving backs out of the back
>> and kind of a get on base kind of
runner. I think Bill's going to get
better, right? McNichols, we see what he
can do for us last year, right? Jerome
Ford is very versatile,
>> explosive player, like kind of in a
backup role, but do they need like a
stud or do they have that guy in there?
Studs are always welcome on my team. All
right, listen to me. I don't care who's
in the room. Listen to me. When I was
drafted, my room was full of studs.
>> That is a That's Talk about that story.
That is a Cuz they handled it well in
free agency, right? All these The room
was full.
>> Yeah.
>> And then they said, "We can draft Fred
Smoot here."
>> Fred Smoot drops to us in the second
round.
>> Yeah.
>> I got Champ Bailey Dale Green Center and
we still going to take him. He's the
best player available. I'm going to take
that stud. I don't care the situation.
Let the situation work itself out. And
when the situation worked itself out,
the two babies started, which was me and
Champ. So, at the end of the day,
>> if I can get Jeremiah Love in that room,
>> look. So,
>> no, but I feel you on that. But that's
the same analogy you you should have
used for the receivers. If you can get a
stud early,
>> Yeah.
>> why not? You know what I mean? You know
what I'm saying? Because you you don't
you don't know. Look, Terry is much
older and his and his contract is what
it was and what it is. And it don't seem
likely like they going to be paying him
the money that he's going to be due next
year anyway. So why not go get that stud
>> if you got to get him at seven? If if if
he's available at seven. So I don't
knock nothing you said about the running
back because guess what? If I get a guy
that going to shift some things in that
running back room, so be it.
>> Has he failed to us? Let me go get him.
You know,
>> the other thing you guys talked about
too which I think is really important is
competition, right? Like You keep
bringing a DAO. You bring in Chase on
and then what does that do for Dorance
Armstrong? Kind of probably turns
>> Oh, turns up. Yeah. Dietri turn it up a
little bit. Right.
>> You bring Tim Sanders in here. Let's
tell him.
You got to understand them older guys.
See that young that young meat come
through that room.
>> They like look here. They go home and
tell the wife it ain't going to beat
them. Christmas going to be uh
they let you know right now. We going to
have to hold off on this B.
>> Don't start thinking too headed cuz I
got to go out here and make this money.
And the money's already given, but I got
to go out here and solidify this check.
And the way they solidified is go out
there and show these young guys, oh old
old woodpecker or whatever on you. Y'all
got the little country slang names.
>> I got to make sure you know you ain't
coming in here and taking nothing. You
know what I'm saying? And I was, trust
me, I was a receiver.
>> You got your I remember how I remember
like it was yesterday.
Cole's are the first person that kind of
like reached out to me when I came in
with the Jets. Like he reached out to me
quick, but we already had that kind of
like Florida State Miami, we done raced
against each other and track meet. So we
knew each other even not knowing each
other. So Cole like, "Hey T, come sit
right here."
>> Bingo. I know Cole just came in a year
ago. Cole ain't really in there.
>> So he's still like, "Look, man, that's
my guy anyway. Come on, sit here."
>> Wayne Cabat was up there in the front.
You had other kind of guys. You had all
type of other guys that was veterans
that I watched. I forgot the guy name is
played with Randy Mos, but he had they
had just they had just brought him in
free agency. So, I'm sitting there like,
"Okay, I'm young bug. I don't know
better."
>> But you can feel the energy from the
older guys like, you know, even though
Wayne and Wayne did a lot for my career.
I mean, once he really got to know me,
he just opened up like a book. Basically
told me everything I needed to do, how
to do it, you know, what to shoot for. I
loved it. But and initially you can tell
he was being like like I'm gonna keep
you.
>> He felt your presence.
>> I'm gonna keep you. And then when he saw
me Yeah.
>> like go how I worked he was like oh okay
>> this guy's he's respectable. He's not
out here being no cuz you know they was
you're a first round pick. They want to
see you go out there and you know do
>> I need to see why.
>> And after a couple of practices he kind
of like say right here I got you. You
know what I'm saying? So, so, but with
all that being said, the defensive guys
I heard more of the barking and the
chirping from cuz they was like, "We
want to see something, young fella."
Like, you know what I mean?
>> Cuz what people fail to realize, those
Jet teams I was on, it was good, bro.
Like, out of four years of me being
there went to three postseasons. Two of
them we went to the second round. You
see what I'm saying? So, you have one
year that that we didn't go to the
postseason, but but we was good. We was
one of those teams that
>> we was a a play away from being in that
that that extra
>> that that third game.
>> Yeah. and probably a chance to go to the
Super Bowl. Same way here in 2005 how we
was a play away from beating Seattle,
you know what I mean? So
>> yeah, we know y we turned into the Jets
getting Yeah. start getting guys from
the Jets. So when I So when I hear
having those opportunities, that's why I
feel the way I feel about getting
>> talent and uh competition in your room
cuz it doesn't do nothing but
>> bring out the best in everybody.
>> If you didn't have a fire up underneath
you, you got one now. You know what I
mean? I ain't got to say nothing. as a
coach. I'm going put a I'mma put one
piece in the room and guess watch
everybody just kind of like sitting up.
>> I think that's the other thing like Dan
Quinn talks a lot about and so does Adam
Peters about competition
>> and like you want competitive dudes
because competitive dudes get better,
right? They don't stay the same.
>> Like if I got a guy in here that's going
to be like
>> like doesn't like like wilts under the
pressure.
>> Yeah.
>> I don't Yeah.
>> I don't want that. Right. And so again,
we want to build that competitive
environment. Okay. So last question then
we're going to move on is what's the
importance of riding kind of this this
momentum of the offseason, right? Two
new coaches, all these new pieces, guys
with good roles. Like we see visions, we
see a path to success.
>> It's just excitement. All right. It it
it's it lights a fire under the fan base
to say, "All right, we're making moves.
We're making changes. All right, things
didn't go the way we wanted to last
year. We're not going into this year
with the same group. We're not going
into this year with the same vision.
We're going in here with a different
vision." And I think it just lights the
the fan base up and lets them know, hey,
we working to get better. How much
better? We don't know yet, but we're
trying to do everything we can do. We
went out, we uh kind of got our
weaknesses better. We stren we we
strengthened the weaknesses. Uh we
brought in new coaches. We brought like
we're trying everything we can do to not
get back to where we was two years to
excel farther than we was two years ago.
So that's the whole thing about it.
>> To me, I think I'm going to piggyback.
I'm going to interject off what Tana
said earlier. It's like, "Yeah, we won
this. Let's build on this. Take it to
the draft. Once we take it to the draft,
let's take it to the whatever season."
And then if we can just keep building
that good players, adding good players,
young players, it's coming together.
We're coaching the offense. We're
coaching the defense. We're
communicating. We're carrying this
energy. We got a shot.
>> Yeah.
>> I, you know, I to me it's like them
saying, "Okay, you guys was upset with
how we handled things last year." I
think Fency we made good moves last
year.
>> I think you know quietly we we made
moves last year in Fery that told us
that we going to have another good
season. You see what I'm saying?
>> I think what you do with the momentum we
having right now and you took it before
I got a chance to say it. I was going to
say the same thing about yeah let's lead
over to the d. No do that. Let's lead
over to the draft. But beyond the draft
we have to set fire in the coach's room
too. Hey you can't co whatever you did
last year if you still around here can't
have the same thing. You got to be
better. You know what? Uh, as a whole,
whatever we did in preseason as a team
before we got to play a game, we got to
be better. So, I think that's what I
want to see this do. I want to see
>> this initiative that they made to go out
there and and dominate what what fans
and everybody said that they did in the
free agency that dominate when it come
to getting these acquisitions. Let's go
out here and put them to work. Let's go
out here and get our best product on the
field because it's not good to just have
that shiny car in my garage if I can't
go ride it and show everybody what it's
made of. You see what I'm saying? I
don't want to get the fast car that I'm
going to ride speed limit.
>> Yeah.
>> Why?
>> Why? See what I'm saying?
>> So, I'm not trying to just have you
here. I'm trying to get you out here and
play your best or be your best so we can
be our best.
>> Yeah.
>> Drop mic.
>> He just laughed.
>> He did drop. because of that. But
because Tanner just put that picture of
the goat change in the group chat.
>> Y
Hey, listen. They don't know how group
because No, I'm going to be real with
you. I'm the dude that don't I don't I
don't shoot. You know what I'm saying?
>> I ain't a shooter. That's You know what
I mean? You a shooter. All you do
shooting. SHOOTING.
>> I'M ON THERE. I SEE a t-shirt with a
rank of bacon that collar on there. ALL
KINDS OF STUFF. I JUST GET SHOT AT ALL
THE TIME ON THE TECH TREE. Is that your
shirt?
>> I'm shooting the dead.
>> No, that's the shirt BLUE FOOT PUT ON.
>> HE WAS TALKING ABOUT YOUR shirt
>> talking about talking about it came from
a dead man. I mean, you done talking
about the dead man suit award so many
years people got to get back at you.
>> AND THAT'S FINE. THE ONE THING I LEARNED
AS a trans talker, if you don't if you
can't take it, do not dish it.
>> Yeah, 100%.
>> Do not dish it.
>> All right, break two. This is pivotal
cuz
>> this is pivotal. That's all I got to
say.
>> Huddle up team. It's time to call it
winter audible because when the temps
drop, the real magic kicks off. West
Virginia. Think trails that crunch like
game day turf. Ski runs for level for
every level of fan. And cozy cabins that
won't break your budget. I SEE YOU
THERE, FRED.
Trade lift lines, chaos for wide open
slopes, and hot cocoa breaks by
crackling fires and a mountains dress
in a blanket of pure white. So grab your
squad,
pack your cold weather swag, and head to
almost heaven this winter in West
Virginia.
>> It's so good.
>> I hate YOUR GUT. HEY,
you know what's so good about this?
And it's crazy because we made this out
of competition when you really ain't we
just I want to do the rigs good
regardless.
>> But I love when you stumble.
>> GOT HIM.
>> FRED BE OVER THERE. HE DIDN'T want to
jump out his seat. I I see him over
THERE AND JERKING. HE CAN'T help
himself.
>> He loves to hear stumble. Y'all when he
get his bear white arm the best.
>> He start reading slow.
>> Yeah.
>> I like this. this.
>> Huddle up, team.
>> No, hot cocoa.
>> It's good. It's good. I feel like I'm
there. I feel like I'm ready TO GO.
>> IT FEEL LIKE WE in West Virginia.
>> That's what it feels like.
>> All right, let's see what we can do.
>> You said they were going to Geico is
going to get everything.
>> They going to get everything I got. But
I might have to reup his read. So, so
it's perfect. You know what I'm saying?
>> You know, isn't it strange? People
really want to save money, but are so
willing to toss their hard-earned coin
into a three-foot pool of
disappointment. You don't need to throw
your money away. All you need is your
phone. Go to Geico, get a quote, and you
could save 900 of your on your phone. It
feels good to save some coin. It feels
good to Geico,
>> Fred.
>> I actually like that.
>> Yeah, I like that. I don't know if it
was the voice. I don't know. You had put
a little another p to your voice.
>> Yeah. I had some some peaks and
>> b we listen we listen we listen
>> we listen to the commas. We listen to
the dashes.
>> It was really nice man.
>> That's but it is a strange read.
>> Yeah. Yeah. We we we like Geico. But
that we in terms of competition West
Virginia's
>> it's just a structured read. It's
telling a story. Take us on a journey.
>> Hot cocoa.
All right. Can't stop, won't stop.
Brought to you by the US Army. Be
tested, but not just on paper. Be strong
and more than muscle. Be courageous and
supported by a mighty team. Be all you
can be. Visit goarmmy.com to learn more.
Okay, so we get some questions from fans
on YouTube, on Instagram, on the uh on
the podcast networks, right?
>> Appreciate those questions. And this is
one that came up. Can you win right away
with this much change?
>> Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. That's the new
NFL.
>> Do you have an example of that?
>> All right. Seattle Seahawks.
>> All right. Seattle Seahawks, the head
coach has been there two years. The
quarterback has been there one year. All
right. Uh that defense has been put
together in the last three years. At the
end of the day, we talking about instant
cocoa and instant grits. Now, now if you
got the right head coach and you got the
right quarterback and the rest of your
team falls in line, you can win right
now. I take you on example. Two years
ago, we got the right head coach, we got
the right quarterback. We went to the
NFC Championship. At the end of the day,
you can turn the page like the NBA now
and you can go from worst to first.
That's what this league is about right
now. All you need is the right
structure, right leadership, and right
talent.
>> Yeah. I I was going to say we don't have
to look that far. We we actually got a
chance to do it. I mean, we we we are
witnesses to this can be done. We had a
huge turnover when it came to the guys
that we brought in here two years ago,
and they went out there and flat out
played ball. So, it's just one of those
things, man. I I I I I think I took back
I look back and I take a lot from that
season and the one thing was just about
the culture.
>> Mhm.
>> You know what I mean? That's the most
important thing to me. It's the culture.
It's what you set for all these guys.
That one standard that you got to say
this is what we live by.
>> This is what we die by. You know, and we
use them slangs on the football field
like as if we out there in real battle,
but we know we trying to, you know, say
to each other, you know. And every time
we sat down in these chairs and had a
guy in here that we sat, you know, and
talked to, they talked about that
camaraderie. They talked about that
brotherhood. They talked about the
culture. And we saw it instantly. I
mean, we had been here. We've been here
longer than anybody.
>> And
>> we ain't have a culture.
>> Yeah.
>> We ain't have a culture.
>> No.
>> We had a bunch of guys that, you know,
what our culture was outside of these
walls when we go out and hang out. Yeah.
And you would see them same guys that
hung out. Yeah.
>> Kind of showing that on the field. They
they was out there each other
individually seeing like, okay, my guy
who I'm going to go have this, you know,
throw a couple of back with,
>> I can't just have him go out there and
ball and I don't show up too. You know
what I mean? So, you can see the same
group of guys competing. I remember at
one point in time, Coach Gibbs had this
best. And this is when I knew it was
different here.
>> And remember, my first three years here
was with Coach Gibbs. And offensively,
you know, we ain't have nothing. He say,
"I just got to get three guys the ball.
Got to get Porters 20 something plus
carries. Tanner and and Kulie got to get
at least 15 attempts."
>> Yeah.
>> A piece.
>> Mhm.
>> And we should be able to win the game.
>> And I'm sitting there saying to myself,
>> "Boy, if that's all we got, cuz you
know, I didn't I wasn't used to that in
New York. In New York, don't get me
wrong, Curtis Martin was going to have
his but El Boogie come in and get at
least 10 touches, 15 touches. Um, you
know, Wayne going to do his thing in the
slot on third down. He going to move the
chains. Cole don't go across the middle
and catch some something and then break
a tackle and score, but we got to get
that that that bomb to Tanner. We got to
get a reverse. We got like we had so
many different guy. And then we had
Anthony Beck at tight end. We got to get
him in the red zone. He's going to be
our guy that, you know, he can catch the
ball over middle. So, we had so many
pieces to that offense. And then we had
Chad or Vinnie that was going Chad was
going to orchestrate the ball. He was
going to he was going to methodically
move the ball from one goal line to the
next like with without a doubt. We if we
backed up, Chad going to get 12 first
down. I'm not even sure if that many
first downs on the field, but he going
to move the ball that way. Like that's
how he did things. He didn't care about
the big play.
>> When we had Vinnie in there starting,
>> don't snooze.
>> Test the verdict going to let that
>> snooze. I told you was T ver would tell
me all the time, look tenner, you know,
you know, I might come back to you. And
every time he was coming backside, bombs
over bad. That's how he like it.
>> You see what I'm saying? So that's how
he like it.
>> When you see that being done
>> at a high level with so many guys and
then you get to a team and you only
three of you got to go out there and
make it happen, it's critical.
>> Well, we was a we was a defensive uh le
team. That's what we did. We played
defense.
>> But but my thing is with that, just
saying go back to to the whole point I'm
trying to make is it's a difference when
you have a coach. It's a difference when
I'm not dependent on one and two guys to
make this thing go. You see what I'm
saying? That's why I love the committee
in the back field and the committee at
receivers. I love when Chad I mean when
um when when Calm got here,
>> when PL went down, it was no it was no
drop. Every receiver still went out
there and ball. You know what I'm
saying? And when he got back, it just
made us that much more better. So, you
know, so I it's the culture for one
thing, the brotherhood, but I think
collectively, man, that's what make you
got to go out there and do what you do.
>> Yeah. is what I would say about this is
like can you run right wide away I agree
with Fred I agree with Tana the culture
is really important it it is hard though
yeah
>> you got to like work on the brother like
this is the where the last two years are
important like the culture everyone
talks about you can bring those guys in
get them integrated right
>> the coaching you got to make sure you
coach your face off get guys integrated
with new defensive and offensive schemes
and I trust Dan that he hired two people
that he feels like can get that done so
is it hard
>> yes is it doable also yes especially if
you get what is it like um I like doing
hard [__] with good people says This is
a hard thing.
>> Yes. Winning in the NFL each g each
quarter like it's just hard.
>> I mean shoot each play
>> each play like it just it's just hard
man. So at the end of the day I know it
looks easy while you're sitting on your
couch.
>> Yeah.
>> And you're watching it and you can see
the big flow of everything but when you
out there in traffic
>> it's different, man. It's a different
deal.
>> I I tell you this and y'all tell me how
y'all feel about it whenever. But I
almost feel like last year was it was it
was meant to happen.
>> Yeah.
>> Because anytime you have some good the
way we had it that first year, you got
to experience a little let down
>> trial and it like sometimes it's it's
it's it's given a little differently.
You might get that let down out the gate
and then now you know how to build from
that.
>> But when you have when you're on a high
horse,
>> you got that much success
>> and you've been knocked off that quick,
it hurts. It's like you don't want to
you don't necessarily want to be back
that high, but you want to make sure you
climbing every time you get a chance to
go back after it. And now you want to
make sure that every ch opportunity on
the field is better than that last
opportunity. See what I'm saying? Like
whatever you did,
>> I used to do this when I got hurt.
>> I didn't necessarily I used to have in
my head I you know I told you I have a
weird way of going about things. I would
cut family members just to go out there
and be great. I'm being real with you.
if you in my line on my dial who I'm
going to talk to through the week, don't
call me because that wasn't helpful for
me to be successful. I didn't do it in
college. I I didn't do it over there.
So, I don't want I don't want that done
now. So, when I start seeing that
>> things of that nature work for me,
>> I took it to my game. So, with us, when
I with me, when I got off that injury, I
was like, I got to get I got to get back
to 42 Tanner,
>> start popping everything. I'm talking
about quad win. Yeah.
>> Hamstream with
>> Then I slowed down again. I said, "Okay,
>> what I need to do every day, I got to
stack.
>> Got to stack them." You know what I
mean? Just get out there and have a good
good practice.
>> Yeah.
>> Get out there and catch two balls today.
Like I didn't want to have a, you know,
10 catch practice. Catch two of them cuz
guess what? Three and four going to
come. You know what I mean?
>> So the first game, just get out there
and play the whole game.
>> You know what I mean?
>> Oh, I scored a touchdown. I ain't expect
it. next week play the whole game and
and and be a guy that you know be a
differencemaker. Oh man, I was more than
a difference. So now if you just
stacking them and you thinking you
thinking solely about that that that
day, you get a chance to see a season of
greatness. You see what I'm saying?
Instead of going out there saying, "Oh,
we got to be better." No, the whole big
picture. It it it's day by day, week by
week. You know what I'm saying? Game by
game, month by month. You know how we we
put them in quarters for a reason. Yeah,
let's put let's put a great quarter,
four games together that we can say,
"Okay, this going to give us a chance to
go in the second quarter and we trying
to be 500 again." You know, before you
know it, we sitting in a good position.
We're the tops of talks when it comes to
going to the postseason.
>> Well, here go crazy thing. I'll never
forget when I first came back here.
>> I had I was just coming off of my broke
jaw.
>> Yeah. Talking about the day when I
bummed you in the first
>> He bummed me. And that what I was gonna
bring up. So, I I'm lining up. I had
already been feeling great cuz I ain't I
ain't realized putting my helmet on my
balance was gone
>> and I line up first play me and Tanner
right at each other and I like in my
head I'm like this what you asked for.
They going to sit they going to sit in
it deep and I never get he came OUT THE
LINE. YEAH. YEAH. YEAH. So now I'm
chasing him and I all I SEE IS ELBOW AND
NECK and I like this boy done beat me
bad out here. And I realized
>> I need to get my balance back like
because it's it's gone. So I just used
to just sit in the locker room with my
helmet on because I just I wasn't used
to it no more. And that was just coming
off a a broke jaw. So it's just small
things like that.
>> Yeah. I always tell my son like you you
learn more from uh failures than you do
success all the time. Like cuz again
like that's something's wrong with your
process, you can fix it. Like Tana's
talking about there you're talking
about, right? Like and I do think like
when you look at this is one thing I
love about Dan, right? is like he
identified some issues. He said we have
to change these things. He made those
changes. Adam seems to have learned.
They brought in some younger, more
talented pieces, spent a little bit more
money, and all of a sudden it's like,
man, more opt more optimistic here. So,
I think that's the great thing. And
again, can you win after a lot of
turnover and change? Yes.
>> Yes. But it's going to be tough. But I
do think you've got the right people
making the right decisions to get that
done. All right. So, this is another
question. Um, what is the most important
constant? Is it the quarterback? Is it
the head coach, GM, offensive
coordinator? What do we got?
>> Oh, both. Uh, if you can keep
continuity, I don't care.
>> But I I think specifically like to cut
you off like the head coach and the
quarterback like keeping like I think
about like the best ones. Yeah.
>> Like think about, you know, Bill
like Yeah. If you can keep I'm going
tell you what a quarterback and a head
coach staying together says. One,
longevity. Two, uh, you're consistently
winning. Because if you're not
consistently winning, y'all y'all are
not together that long. All right. So
that's showing me if they are together
and y'all got a long track record, it
must be a track record of winning.
>> And and so I can't say one is is more
than the other because I always tell
people, why do you have to pick one? I I
shouldn't have to pick Bill Bellich or
Tom Brady. Why can't they come together
to form Voltron? Like at the end of the
day, why can't all pieces work in
unison? A lot of 90s cartoon references.
>> Yeah. I'm just saying Hawks is one of my
favorite too also. You know what I'm
saying?
>> Yeah. I just Yeah. I mean,
>> I would say like if you had to say
individually, it's always the
quarterback. I think quarterback any
coach.
>> You know what I mean? I think
>> it's got to be the right guy though.
>> It has to be the right guy because you
can't just put a guy in there who who's
not a uh I guess a leader of men and say
that's go out here and win cuz you know
the team ain't going to operate or or
basically do what they got to do. But
when you have both quarterback in place
and the and the head coach, it gives you
uh that much more of an opportunity to
go out there and and do like I said
earlier, stack wins and and put it
together. And that's why I said it's so
to me when it comes down to just I feel
like we have that like man I was I was I
was a big fan of dance before he got
here. You know what I mean? Like I I saw
what he did with the Legion Boone.
>> I saw what he did
>> taking him to the Super Bowl.
>> I saw what he did in Atlanta. I I saw
instantly what he did defensively to the
Cowboys cuz that had been their Achilles
Hill for years. I mean, you could Romo,
no matter who was at quarterback, BLO,
no matter who was back there
defensively, they couldn't stop nobody,
you know? And I used to say that all the
time, like, look, bro, we could just
beat their defense.
>> No matter what they do offensively, you
know what I mean? Like, they just go out
here and dominate their defense, which
that's how we was able to be in those
games back then with Dallas. And it was
an instant change. I'm talking about
almost instantly. I'm like, this defense
look different. you know, I'm watching
the games and not even knowing who's,
you know, that's before I was, you know,
just in tune with just going every day
about, you know, what's going on, who we
facing, what's, you know, who's the
coaches in this division.
>> Then I heard Dan Quinn. I'm like, I know
that damn name from somewhere. You know
what I'm saying? I'm like, uh, I knew
this defense was different. You know
what I mean? This is why, you know? So,
>> just look at the players after he left.
Trayvon Diggs ain't been the same. Bla
ain't bitten dirt.
>> And I think too, you can just look at
>> um
>> that's why I kind of scratching my head
too, how things is going to will we get
a little bit of Dan's defense
>> on top of uh with the kid the guy we
brought in
>> Jonte Jones. Jonte.
>> Yeah. Like will we get a will we get a
combination of of both what he learned
in Minnesota and
>> Of course you will. Your head coach
always going to leave
>> because I just I think that was
something that stood out to me last year
when Dan got in there. we was running
the same stuff, but it was just the way
he called it attention to detail when he
called it. Like he brought that blitz at
the right time when we was over there in
Spain and it was like it was instant,
you know, success like. So I just want
to see that again from us cuz I feel
like but I also understand last year
when we didn't have a lot of guys to
really lean on.
>> We was out there, man. We was
>> trying to survive. The difference
between survival and dominating.
>> We was literally treading water the
whole year.
>> This whole year, man.
>> I'm just trying to stay
>> keep this boat afloat.
>> You know what I'm saying? So, but I
think it's both. I, you know, I know I
said a lot. I just think it's both. I
think when you have a Jaden Dangs, man,
that's why I say, man, I just hope he go
out there and just take a little bit
like like that page that I had to take
it out. Look, man, I ain't trying to be
Jaden from rookie season. I'm just
trying to stack days,
>> be a better version, you know what I'm
saying? Every week I want to stack a
week, you know?
>> Yep. So, obviously, we're excited. Think
we could win right now. Great free
agency period. We're going to talk about
the draft here in a second. Do a little
mock draft mock.
>> But in the meantime, we're going to pay
some bills. Let's get to this third ad
break.
>> You know, you should be actually doing
both of the third break reads.
>> Why is that?
>> Because then you you catch up with us
two a piece. Me and Tana two a piece.
>> I got to do the intro. No one wants to
hear me do two of these in a row. I'll
do another one a different block if you
want next time.
>> All right. All right. Huddle up,
Commanders fans. The Commanders Golden
Pass raffle operated by the Virginia
Lottery gives you a chance to win the
ultimate fan experience. That means
tickets, VIP treatment, special
appearances by Washington legends such
as ourselves, and much, much more.
Limited tickets are available. So visit
vaottery.com/commanders
to enter the raffle today. That's
and break. That was pretty good, man.
That's pretty good. That's better than
last week.
>> They say your work defines who you are.
Monday through Friday, 9 to5, you're
clocking in. But what happens on the
weekend? What happens to your time? You
could take it easy or you could use that
time to get better. Right, Fred?
>> Right.
>> In the US Army, we think differently.
Your time should be used to improve the
skills you do have and learn some you
don't to push yourself in new ways
because it's those days that truly
define who you are. That's how you make
progress. That's how you make an impact
on the world around you. It's your time.
How you spend it up to you. It's your
time. the US Army Reserve.
>> You know what? I think a old NFL injury,
your broken nose of 17 times, I think it
causes you to read bad.
>> You think so?
>> Yeah.
>> Gets a little nasly sometimes. Get a
little Why you trying to say the man
read bad? I think the man read perfectly
fine.
>> I'm just saying. You know what he's
doing though, right?
>> It feel like accident.
>> He saw He saw those that thing up.
>> All those praises you guys made. He felt
a little left out. He like I gave him my
all last last week.
>> I do think you got a shot this week
though. Usually I don't think so. I
think I think there's an opportunity
about your game.
>> No, he killed it.
>> All right. So now we're doing with um
producer Jason at the helm of this mock
draft with PFF. Yeah.
>> We got Command Center podcast mock
draft. We do one of these every week on
the drive to the draft podcast which is
our draft ccentric podcast. Fred's going
to be on that show next week. He did a
great job. We did our guaranteed
ballers, which he has won two years in a
row, which really just guts me.
>> I know. I know. It just guts me.
>> Just draft guru. I'm sorry.
>> He's just coming out with just some
craziness every week. But anyway, so
we're going to do a five round mock as
the commanders. That seems like a lot,
but we only have three picks. Yeah,
>> in five rounds. So, this should go.
>> That could change.
>> It could It could change.
>> It could change.
>> And I hope that it does change, but
we'll see. As of right now, though, we
only have three picks. I think 77 71 and
then like 156
something like that.
>> So
let's get her started.
>> Are we going to get hit this up or we
got to sign rolls here? Jason, what we
got? Oh, we're just we're on the clock.
We're in it, dude. Okay, so at seven
we've got David Bailey, Francis Maui,
Noah, Caleb DS, and we got
>> And I am going to do Mansor Delane,
Dylan Theamman, Spencer Fono, Monroe
Freeling.
>> Hey, let's just go.
>> I think it's a good idea to tell them
who went in the first six pits.
All right, man. Those who went to the
first pick. I don't think that shocked
anybody. Orville Reese. Uh Jeremiah Love
at three. I think
>> I think that's becoming more of a thing.
>> Yeah. And then you got Ruben Bang going
to Tennessee at four.
>> Sunny Styles at New York, which I really
think that's a legit chance that he goes
to New York. And Cornell Tate at six to
the Cleveland Browns.
>> They need a lot of things the Cleveland
Browns, but I think that bodess really
well for us.
>> Nice. Well, you got to realize why would
they go double D the ends when they
already got Miles Gary.
>> So, I was thinking about that earlier
like if I'm them, I'm really giving
Ruben I'm talking about the Cleveland
Browns. I'm really giving Ruben Bane a
good look cuz the idea of Ruben Bane
>> across from Miles Gar
>> and just wreaking havoc in that division
physical like there's something about
that. But, however,
>> for the commanders, yeah, if David
Bailey
>> is on the board,
>> run it up.
>> I know people want that logo on the TV
for a long time. I'm putting my track
spot. I'm not getting somebody else, not
me, but I'm getting maybe
>> maybe Santana
number one pick
>> to just gas his way up there. Get that
pick in as soon as possible.
>> If if David Bailey is there, don't even
let the Browns finish the last name
Tate. When they say Tate, we say Bailey.
All right, get it in there right now.
>> So, will y'all be surprised if Bane go
before Bailey? Cuz I've been hearing
like more more so.
>> I would be surprised a little bit, but
it really is like flavor. So, David say,
who do you like? So David what you do
>> has 15 sacks 77 pressures like
>> he's just a pass maybe but they would
say Bane plays the run
>> plays everything
>> better than than
>> so so Cleveland might want a guy that
does a little more just just to get out
to the quarterback.
>> I think he went to Tennessee.
>> I mean Tennessee my bad. Yeah went to
Tennessee. So again I think that's I
think Tennessee is on the board for an
edge. So like Arll Reese Bane or Bailey.
>> Yeah.
>> I personally think they probably go
Bailey or a Reese. I think they go
Bailey
>> because of Salah's defense, but if
they've got a higher grade, then I think
this bodess really well for us here at
six. Again, the other guy to talk about
here would be Caleb DS.
>> Maybe the best film in the class, Jason
uh Johnson, producer Jason,
>> I'm going to say man Delany now. I think
he just made his
>> Yeah, he just made himself
>> So, we just recorded this. We're
recording this 43 you ran the other day.
>> Yeah. What's the movie?
>> And long smooth. And what's crazy is his
film. Like he plays with great
anticipation, great feel. Like he
doesn't play like a fast guy,
>> but he doesn't back down. That's what I
love about
>> Yeah. He's a really good player.
>> Yeah.
>> I just think edge rusher value
>> is there
>> and the consistency of it and get that
pass rush here. Have a fourman rotation
on the perimeter. Like I think that
makes this group significantly better
right out the gate.
>> Can I ask a question? Go ahead. I know
you say you're sending Santana to sprint
this name up. Oh yeah.
>> What if that phone rings?
Yeah. And someone someone really wants
Bailey and they're moving into that
spot. Let's see.
>> How many spots?
>> I'd pick it up.
>> Let's say it's Cincinnati that's picking
right there at 10. They want they want
>> Can they give me a second round pick?
>> Well, that's what I'm saying. Like, are
you entertaining phone call?
>> If I can get a second round pick and
move back to 10.
>> Well, you can have that thing right now.
We ain't got to talk.
>> I'm in. Although I think Bailey's pretty
special. I can move back to 134 and and
get that second round pick because then
I become part of the Kenyan Sadique
>> sweep stakes.
>> Dude, you and Kenyan Sadique.
>> I'm just telling you.
>> So Fred's trying to manipulate the whole
draft to draft the tight end.
>> So So I'm going to say, boy, you going
to mess the whole room up. I know it's
getting studs, but I feel like when you
have what we have and the added guy,
chick, like you don't really need to.
>> I like I said, I don't need him.
>> Yeah. But yeah, 134. He the best player
>> with another with another pick. Yeah, I
guess.
>> Yeah. And I got my second round pick.
>> Are we doing trades in this or no?
>> No. Okay.
>> But we will do that on our drive to the
draft podcast. We'll do a bunch of
trades. So, I guess my philosophy
question for you guys is, is there a
player in this draft where you're like,
I'm not entertaining trades. This guy's
just a blue chipper. I'm taking him
here.
>> David Bailey is probably the closest for
me. I mean, obviously Jeremiah Love, I
think the same thing with styles. Yeah.
as soon as they stop.
>> So
>> that second round pick to me when you
have so much so many that
>> need to be filled
>> it's really enticing to get
>> here go think about it I want to say if
I'm in the top 10 I always say I want to
leave with a freakish player
>> freak I feel like this draft got five of
them meaning they are
>> who we got who are they
>> Jeremiah Love okay
>> anomaly all right I feel like David
Bailey
>> is a freak Kenyan Sadique is a freaky
styles is a freak and Rel.
>> So you think you think Kenyan Sadi is a
top five player in this draft?
>> I just think his freakish athletic
ability.
>> Wow. You're really in on him?
>> I I really am.
>> So you would take him higher than Brock
Bowers? I
>> I DON'T CARE WHERE BROCK WENT. I TOLD
YOU WHAT BROCK WAS WHEN WE CAME OUT. I
TOLD YOU I WOULD HAVE TOOK BROCK number
one if I had to pick cuz I was just so
in love with his skill set and I thought
he was just But I think I think Brock
skill set and his play kind of showed
the same.
>> Yeah.
>> You have to look at did did Sadi play
show what he did testing
>> wise. When when Brock Byus was was
featured, he was the go-to guy.
>> Yeah.
>> Sadique had to kind of share it. He had
guys on the outside. He had running
backs. He had to kind of share the load
when Brock B.
>> So he was held back a little bit because
he couldn't he couldn't show us.
>> We talked about well I mean Lad Maki was
in that offense too in Georgia. But I
will say this when you watch Keny and
Sadiq very fast physical line
>> put together
>> has a hard
>> you don't feel like he got the wiggle
>> has a hard time putting his foot in the
ground
>> and that gets me a little bit nervous.
I'm not saying he's going to be a bad
pro but I just get a little bit nervous
about that. So I I feel great if we
trade it back to 12 and he's sitting
there. Maybe let's have a talk about it.
But for this, if this is the case, David
Bailey for me. Everyone good with that?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, I'm good with I'm good with
Bailey.
>> Yeah, Bane ain't there. I'm good with
>> You want to take Bane, huh?
>> I don't really, you know, I really don't
have nothing. I Any any guy that's
available that's that's considered top
five.
>> How do you feel about Mike Washington?
Top 10.
>> So, let's talk about Let's just talk
about a couple guys that went off the
board. Joshua Joseph, edge rusher from
Tennessee, I think would be an excellent
pick here for Washington. Elijah Serat,
receiver from Indiana.
>> Yeah, we're now in the third round at
pick 71.
>> Pick 71. Antonio Williams, receiver from
uh from Clemson, I think is could be
special. Grayson Holton from Oklahoma,
defensive tackle, kind of three
technique guy. Josiah Trot, one of my
favorite linebackers in the class from
Missouri. And now on the board, we've
got Davidson Igbonosen. We got Mike
Washington Jr., the running back from
Arkansas. Dominique, citrus orange from
Iowa State, big citrus. Keelen Rutled,
the guard from Georgia Tech, who is a
nasty mfer. We got Zachariah Branch
Tanner who reminds me a little bit a
little bit of Tyreek Hill just like
hyper horsepower.
>> I say he But don't you feel like you got
one of those in Jaylen Lane from last
year?
>> I mean I think this I like I like Jaylen
Lane a lot. There's something a little
bit different
>> about the horsepower we're dealing with
here. And I'm not again like it is what
it is.
>> Max Claire tight end from Ohio State. Uh
Romelo Height is really interesting here
too. Ed Rush from Texas State. Connor
Lou,
>> Connor Lou, the center from Auburn.
>> Auburn. Yes. So, there are a lot of good
football players here. I The thing that
I have kind of fallen into here
recently, and I'm just going to I'm
going to I'm going to pour my soul out
to you, you the viewer, and Fred and
Santana here
>> is Mike Washington at 71
>> seems
>> really appealing to me. So, for those of
you who aren't in on the draft process,
>> 340, right?
>> You're a 43. He's 61 61 and a half, 225
lbs. Ah,
>> and has a gear where he is able to
>> kind of take it the distance. If you
watch the Texas game, he's running dudes
clean over like clean.
>> Yeah. Like leaving him in the dust.
>> His vision's a little bit up and down,
but I think
>> he will run to the back of you.
>> I think about explosive elements to this
offense.
>> That is really interesting to me here.
Now, can we look at receivers real
quick, Jason? Because again, that's
another position that I know a lot of
fans have been talking about here at 71.
So, Zachariah Branch, Deion Burks from
Oklahoma, Ted Hurst, again talking about
a big kind of ex Malachi Fields from
Notre Dame, Deshawn Stribbling,
>> Brennan Thompson,
>> Brennan Thompson, fastest man at the
combine,
Daniels from Miami. Like, there are a
lot of good receivers here.
>> So, this is what I'll say. I think you
can get a good receiver. We're just
going to read the 200 and uh 200. What
do we got? Let's go Ty Tyron Montgomery
from John Carroll. He's the 214th player
on PFF's website.
>> He was maybe the best player at the
Senior Bowl.
>> Wow.
>> So, do we want to take a running back
here
>> where there's not a lot of running backs
in this class and maybe take a receiver
in the fifth round would be my question
because there are some good really
really good
>> receivers later in the draft.
>> Yeah. I
>> Any any other positions you guys want to
look at real quick?
>> Well, no. If if if if
you saying that if we getting the steal
with Mike Washington Jr. right there and
he can play.
>> So, I don't know if it's a steal. What I
will say is like I think there are three
really good running backs in this class.
>> Yeah.
>> Jeremiah Love.
>> Prince Price from Notre Dame. What's his
name? Price.
>> No. Jadarian Price.
>> Yeah. Jarian Price. And then Ted Ted uh
Washington. Mike.
>> Mike Washington
>> from Arkansas. Yeah. And I think after
that it's a there are good players, but
it's a little bit of a dip. So, if you
want a game player at the running back
spot, I feel like you have to take him
at 71
>> as opposed to a receiver or a safety
like Jason's got the safeties up for us
right now. There's a lot of good
safeties. Interior offensive line
because again, we're kind of looking in
there too. Corners Davisen
um is a really good player from Ohio
State.
>> Um let's look at an interior offensive
line real quick.
>> Yeah, Rutled Connor Lou, Sam Height is
again a great center from Kansas State.
>> Lou is the guy. Jake Slaughter, if you
gonna take a lineman at this spot need
to be assessed.
>> I tell you one thing though, just seeing
how it can like unfold. Like I would
love to move back and get a second round
pick now. You know what I mean? Like I'm
like so many players, man. Like we can
if we can get two for the price of one.
Come on. Well, that's why we need Tai
Simpson
>> to keep on Tyson. We we are pulling with
Tai Simpson to continue to blow people
away his workouts and he'll coach his
son. You know he can talk that talk. You
know he can get on that chalkboard and
make it happen. Ty Simpson, we are
pulling for you cuz somebody going to
come to seven trying to get Tyson.
>> The other one that was good was Monro
Fring had the good combine and
everyone's talking about him being a top
seven pick. That's good. So people get
those get those names up there. Scooch
them up there. Right. So yeah, I mean um
I think Mike Washington is the pick here
for me. But if you guys feel
differently, speak now or forever hold
your mind.
>> I love some Zachariah Branch. You know
how I feel about Zachariah Branch. That
would be interesting. But
>> would that
third round? So this is hypothetically
we don't have a receiver yet.
>> We do not have a receiver yet. No.
>> Yeah, I want a receiver.
>> But I do think Okay, let's go to the
receivers here real quick
>> cuz I'm looking So I'm looking for a
receiver that I bring in. I I don't look
I don't trust a fifth round receiver
being my
>> being my receiver for the future. You
see what I'm saying? Being a guy that's
gonna take over the hand from from
Terry.
>> Totally agree. I totally agree. And this
is where that second round pick.
>> So I wanted either a first, second or
third round guy. Stud them. That's them
where the studs at.
>> Lotto stud you know them where the studs
at.
>> I think we did this yesterday on our
drive to the draft show. Like to me like
I love the kid from Old Miss Deshawn
Stribbling. I think Jason loves Malachi
Fields. I just think I really think you
can get a guy who's got some juice
later. The problem is you're not picking
in the fourth round.
>> You're picking in the fifth. Jeff
Cobwell from Cincinnati. Is that the big
kid?
>> So he's 6'5,
>> 217 at the combine. Yeah.
>> Ran a 431.
>> Yes.
>> Had a 43 in vertical 112 broad jump.
>> Dude is a mutant.
>> That's what I'm saying.
>> Also, dude,
>> Jeff,
>> efforts efforts a little up and down.
>> No, I don't like his name. HIS NAME
REGULAR. I WANT HIM TO CHANGE A NAME TO
JJ CODWELL. But
>> but uh let's go up to the top of
receivers. So if you want to take a
receiver, obviously Zachariah Branch,
Deion Burks, really good players,
smaller guys. Yeah,
>> Ted Hurst is a freak, man. Yeah.
>> 6'3 around a 4-3 at the combine. Malachi
Fields is 6'5, 220 lbs. Like there's a
guy here for you if you want.
>> I would go probably Ted Hurst. I love I
love small school pedigree. They always
have a chip on their shoulder. That's
how uh Green Bay and Pittsburgh uh
draft. They love small school guys
because they come with a chip on their
shoulder like London Fletcher. So I
would love to have Ted Hurst.
>> Ted Hurst.
>> Yeah,
>> I might go Malachi Fields. If we're
between Ted Hurst,
>> I'm in between.
>> I think Ted H faster than
>> Malachi. He's he's significantly faster.
>> If we trying to go for body types,
something different than what we have in
the room. I'm thinking bigger guy. I say
>> uh Malachi Fields or you know
>> Hurst Deshan
Stribbling, Malachi Fields, Ted Hurst
are big. But if we just going for a
receiver explosive, I'm going with the
I'm going I'm going Z. I'm going Branch.
>> All right. That's a That's a little Tana
clone right there.
>> I think we can all agree on Branch. He's
going to have some special.
>> I feel like even though he's small, his
return kicks from the dope.
skill set is different from all the guys
we have.
>> But he rocked up.
>> That's what I'm saying. He perfect. Love
it.
>> All right, we're going to pick 147 now,
>> which is way down the list here. So
>> down yonder.
>> Dan yonder. Okay, so it's interesting.
EMTT Johnson is the running back from
Nebraska. He's available. Don Bentley,
the tight end from Utah. Both really
solid football players. Uh Tim Kennedy
or Keenan, excuse me, the third from
Alabama as a defensive tackle. He's like
335 lbs. Big old heavy dude.
>> A name that just popped to me as Jason
slowly scrolled down the screen. I see
it
>> is Nicholas Singleton from Penn State.
>> Both bags from Penn State.
>> He broke his foot in this offseason
process, so he hasn't run a 40. Yeah.
But when you look at his like he's on
Feldman's freaks list. He's supposed to
run a sub44.
>> I got to see him in person. Remember I
told you I took my son to Penn Star
though. So I got to see him in person
while while he was fully health. I got
to see both backs and he seemed to be
the faster out of the two.
>> He has the he he was the twitchiest.
>> He's way faster. He's he's explosive
now, but his production has never
matched his physical traits.
>> Yeah.
>> Um can we go to safety real quick? Cuz I
think receivers's deep. I think safety's
deep. If you want a good football
player, maybe safety is one where we can
grab a guy here. Um, okay. So, Cole Wooi
from Texas Tech, good football player.
Bishop Fitzgerald from USA.
>> You don't like Michael Taffy?
>> Uh, dude, you know, Jason really likes
him a lot. I'm a little I worry about I
worry about the athlete. Yeah.
>> You know, and so like if we can get a
freak athlete here, I'd be pretty stoked
on that. Lorenzo Styles, the man who
broke the combine.
>> I don't know if he's going to be hanging
around here. And then maybe my favorite
safety is sitting here, too. Robert
Spears Jennings from Oklahoma.
>> I love him.
>> Yeah,
>> he is a physical like kind of like the
true star box safety. Um kind of could
play linebacker for you.
>> He don't remind you of old Roy Williams,
do he?
>> No, he reminds me a little bit of hope
not
>> Emmenary actually.
>> Oh, he got a profile like Roy.
>> He ran a 43. He's got 33 inch arms.
>> So, and he's 6'2. So, he's a big old hos
who can run a little bit. He's a little
inconsistent as Jason will be very quick
to point out because on the drive to the
draft show Jason said. Don't know about
all that but I'm in on him. So safety.
Uh
>> let's see corner. Let's see corner.
>> Oh. All right. I think corner's shorter
though. You know what I'm saying? Corner
shorter in terms of tail. But let's see
what we got here.
>> And this is for that. What? This is a
fifth round pick.
>> This is a fifth round pick.
>> So if you want some names, Aphesian
Price,
200 lb. He he ran well sub4 540 got long
arms big old hoses respect his game
quite a bit scroll to the top Jason
>> and then uh Devon Marshall is the guy
that you like right Jason am I right
with that
>> I like Marshall too
>> very consistent football player Julian
Neil is a man corner 6'2 205 lbs ran
well at the combine jumped well
>> there are some good players here
>> and in terms of body type that fit kind
of traditional Dan Quinn p um
>> probably be the taller guys
>> pry sock is an excellent fit and I think
he's got a good feel for the position.
>> Yeah.
>> So, I don't know. I'm I'm on board with
Corner if you want to go that direction.
I think he's a good football player.
>> Yeah. I go Washington. I cannot
pronounce his name. Hopefully, the fans
>> Ephesians like
>> Ephesians
>> uh Pric.
>> It's quite the uh quite the name there.
>> Yeah. You know, I like my name.
>> Ephesians.
>> I like my name.
>> So, we went let's see David Bailey at
seven, which is pretty exciting.
Zachariah Branch at 71 to bring some
absolute vertical juice. A little
gadgetry to this offense.
and Ephesians pri sock at 147 long tall
physical corner um who can maybe play on
the perimeter if you need him to. So I
think that's a pretty solid uh draft
right there for us boys.
>> Oh yeah.
>> So stay tuned. We're going to do another
one of these probably in a couple weeks
cuz the draft's coming up. We'll
probably do a trade in that one. But in
the meantime, thank you so much for
joining and consuming the content.
Always appreciate it. Like and subscribe
wherever you watch.
>> But that's it. Peace.
I go. The command center podcast was
filmed at the Big Bear AI command center
studio. Big Bear AI offers mission ready
AI for a rapidly evolving world, proudly
protecting the Washington Commanders and
its fans.